<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_title">
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>title4</item>
        <item>title5</item>
        <item>title5</item>
        <item>title5</item>
        <item>title5</item>
        <item>title5</item>
        <item>title5</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_desc">
<!--        A Star Is Born-->
        <item>
            Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally.
            She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes
            her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side of their
            relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.
        </item>
<!--        Aquaman-->
        <item>
            Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom
            ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer
            the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry,
            Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.
        </item>
<!--        Avengers: Infinity War-->
        <item>
            As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large
            for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos.
            A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts
            of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything
            the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence
            itself has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item>desc4</item>
        <item>desc5</item>
        <item>desc5</item>
        <item>desc5</item>
        <item>desc5</item>
        <item>desc5</item>
        <item>desc5</item>
    </array>
</resources>